<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amazon on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/amazon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amazon on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/amazon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Affiliate Links</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/affiliate-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/affiliate-links/</guid>
      <description>Contains affiliate links, which means that if you click on one of the product links, I’ll receive a small commission at no extra cost to you. Amazon Midwest Grow Kits TubeBuddy Items we suggest you avoid or goto a atlernate vendor Basic Medical Synmax Vinyl Exam Gloves - Latex-Free &amp;amp; Powder-Free - X-Large, BMPF-3004(Case of 1,000),Blue 100 Count these are cheap and break very easily. Unfortunally I bought 1000 of them so I just have to deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coco Coir Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation: An In-Depth Price Comparison</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/buying-coco-coir-blocks-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/buying-coco-coir-blocks-blocks/</guid>
      <description>Coco Coir Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation: An In-Depth Price Comparison Introduction Coco coir, increasingly recognized as an effective substrate for mushroom cultivation, is valued for its moisture retention, pH neutrality, and facilitation of mycelial growth. This guide offers a thorough comparison of coco coir products, focusing on both cost-effectiveness and their appropriateness for different mushroom growing scales.&#xA;Why Coco Coir? Coco coir, a by-product of coconut fiber processing, is known for its excellent water retention, essential for mushroom cultivation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myco Labs Grower&#39;s Select Mushroom 48-Quart Monotub Fruiting Chamber with Filter Disks and Liner</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/mycolabs-growers-select-monotub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/mycolabs-growers-select-monotub/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The 48-Quart Monotub from Myco Labs was my first monotub. This kit is nice, but I do have a few concerns.&#xA;Ordering and Assembly Ordered from Amazon, and it arrived promptly as usual. When it arrived, I had a look and was faced with a decision: to put the plugs in or the filters over the holes. Since I was using a North Spore Organic Lion&amp;rsquo;s Mane Mushroom Spray &amp;amp; Grow Kit, which was already starting to fruit, and I just needed to control moisture levels, I chose to use half the plugs and leave the other holes open, considering that while fruiting, there is not as much risk of contamination.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
