<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Education on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/categories/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Education on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How AI is Helping Mushroom Growers Control Climate</title>
      <link>/post/2026/ai-climate-control-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2026/ai-climate-control-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem-we-all-face&#34;&gt;The Problem We All Face&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well I killed a batch of oyster mushrooms because I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize how quickly humidity could tank. Went from 85% to 60% overnight—took me three days to notice. By then, the fruiting bodies had already aborted. That&amp;rsquo;s when I started thinking: what if something could watch these conditions continuously and actually &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; something before I messed up?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s where AI climate control comes in. And no, I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about some sci-fi setup—I mean actual sensor networks and feedback systems that have gotten smart enough to run themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Mycelium: The Hidden Power Beneath Our Feet</title>
      <link>/post/2024/understanding-mycelium/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/understanding-mycelium/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine a world beneath our feet, intricate and vital, yet unseen. This is the world of mycelium, a fundamental component of our ecosystems. Often overlooked, mycelium is a key player in nature&amp;rsquo;s cycle. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore this fascinating network that lies under the soil.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-is-mycelium&#34;&gt;What is Mycelium?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mycelium is essentially the foundation of the fungi kingdom, much like roots are to plants. These thread-like structures, known as &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hypha&#34;&gt;hyphae&lt;/a&gt;, weave together to form a complex and expansive web. Each hypha is incredibly thin, yet when combined, they create a vast network that can span miles.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
