<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review of Lion&#39;s Mane Mushroom Growing Kit from North Spore</title>
      <link>/post/2024/northspore-lions-mane-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/northspore-lions-mane-kit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024-03-01 Update with &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Midwest Grow Kits&lt;/a&gt; Affilate links.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I embarked on a fascinating journey of mushroom cultivation by purchasing the &lt;strong&gt;Lion&amp;rsquo;s Mane Mushroom Growing Kit&lt;/strong&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;https://northspore.com/collections/beginner-kits/products/grow-your-own-lions-mane&#34;&gt;North Spore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-impressions&#34;&gt;First Impressions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upon arrival, I found the kit contained everything necessary for a novice grower to start immediately. The &lt;strong&gt;clarity of the instructions&lt;/strong&gt; was exceptional, simplifying the setup process. The included spray bottle was perfect for a first-time mushroom grower.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;quality-and-experience&#34;&gt;Quality and Experience&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;substrate-and-mycelium-health&#34;&gt;Substrate and Mycelium Health&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;quality of the substrate&lt;/strong&gt; and the health of the mycelium were impressive. These factors almost guaranteed a successful and bountiful growth. The block was almost solid white, and it was clear it was ready for fruiting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing the Power of UV-C Light in Amateur Mycology</title>
      <link>/post/2024/uvc-handheld-lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/uvc-handheld-lights/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024-03-01 Update with &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Midwest Grow Kits&lt;/a&gt; Affilate links.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;warning-while-uv-c-light-offers-a-non-chemical-no-touch-sterilization-method-its-use-requires-careful-handling&#34;&gt;WARNING: While UV-C light offers a non-chemical, no-touch sterilization method, its use requires careful handling:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety Precautions&lt;/strong&gt;: Always use protective gear, like gloves and safety goggles, to minimize skin and eye exposure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Controlled Usage&lt;/strong&gt;: Limit the duration and frequency of UV-C light exposure to skin to reduce potential health risks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Educate Yourself&lt;/strong&gt;: Understand the implications of UV-C light use, including the potential cancer risk, and follow guidelines for safe operation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;understanding-uv-c-light-a-mycologists-ally&#34;&gt;Understanding UV-C Light: A Mycologist&amp;rsquo;s Ally&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the fascinating world of amateur mycology, maintaining a sterile environment is paramount. One innovative tool gaining popularity in this field is UV-C light, known for its remarkable ability to neutralize bacteria, viruses, and mold. In this post, we delve into the science behind UV-C light and its practical applications in mushroom cultivation, particularly highlighting products from Midwest Grow Kits.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
