<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oregon on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/oregon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oregon on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/oregon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Oregon&#39;s Drug Policy: The Push to Amend Decriminalization</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregaon-rollback-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregaon-rollback-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: The information presented here is intended for informational purposes only and not as legal advice. The legal landscape is continually evolving, especially concerning drug policies. It&amp;rsquo;s essential to conduct personal research and seek professional counsel for specific legal guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;revisiting-oregons-drug-policy-the-push-to-amend-decriminalization&#34;&gt;Revisiting Oregon&amp;rsquo;s Drug Policy: The Push to Amend Decriminalization&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a bold move that once positioned Oregon at the forefront of drug reform in the United States, the state&amp;rsquo;s drug decriminalization law, enacted through Measure 110, is now under reconsideration. The recent legislative attempts to roll back aspects of this law reflect a nuanced struggle between various factions within the state, sparking debates on public health, safety, and the role of criminal justice in addressing drug addiction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice. The laws in Oregon, as with most places, are constantly changing, so do your own research and contact legal representation always.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;oregon-psilocybin-2024-update-navigating-new-mushroom-laws-and-program-insights&#34;&gt;Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oregon&amp;rsquo;s landmark decision to legalize psilocybin for therapeutic use under Measure 109 has set a precedent for psychedelic therapy in the United States. As we navigate through 2024, significant updates to Oregon&amp;rsquo;s mushroom laws have unfolded, presenting both advancements and challenges in the program&amp;rsquo;s implementation. We are highly disturbed by the lack of inclusion of the right for small batch personal usage home growth and ask who stands to benefit most! As usual, big money is running the show, and you will need to have deep pockets to play.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
