<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beginners Guide on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/beginners-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beginners Guide on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/beginners-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Growing Golden Teacher Mushrooms</title>
      <link>/post/2025/growing-gteachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/growing-gteachers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;growing-golden-teacher-mushrooms&#34;&gt;Growing Golden Teacher Mushrooms&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Golden Teacher mushrooms have become popular among home growers thanks to their relatively easy cultivation process and distinctive golden caps. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to grow these fascinating fungi at home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-youll-need&#34;&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Growing Golden Teacher can be easy or hard, given your likely just learning lets do it the easy way. Get your self a all in one grow bag, personally I have been using &lt;a href=&#34;https://zombiemyco.com&#34;&gt;zombiemyco.com&lt;/a&gt; grow bags and have had good results. More importantly the one issue I did have they made it right. Lots of companies say they stand by their product it seems Zombie actually does. This bag &lt;a href=&#34;https://zombiemyco.com/products/mushroom-grow-bag-5lb&#34;&gt;5lb Grow bag&lt;/a&gt; is perfect for starting out. I am no affiliated with the at all as of March 02, 2025, maybe if you mention me in your purchase they can change that. Next you need some liquid culture, sure you can do spores but don&amp;rsquo;t just don&amp;rsquo;t for your first try. Its been a long time since I have actually purchases any liquid culture so I can not really suggesting anyone at this time. If you really want to go with spores I highly suggest &lt;a href=&#34;https://inoculatetheworld.com/product/golden-teacher-isolated-syringe/&#34;&gt;inoculatetheworld&lt;/a&gt; another company who I know stands behind their products.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Does It Cost to Start Growing Mushrooms?</title>
      <link>/post/2024/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting your journey into mushroom cultivation can be both exciting and cost-effective. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a hobbyist looking to grow a few mushrooms for personal use or someone aiming to dive into a more serious cultivation setup, understanding the initial investment is crucial. Here, we&amp;rsquo;ll break down the costs and provide insights into what you can expect when setting up your own mushroom growing operation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started-with-a-grow-kit&#34;&gt;Getting Started with a Grow Kit&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those who are new to mushroom growing, a grow kit is a fantastic way to start. These kits are user-friendly and come with everything you need to grow your first batch of mushrooms. Prices for grow kits typically start at around $30. You can find reliable kits &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/SimpleKit&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Using this referral link helps support us at no extra cost to you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
