<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DIY on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/categories/diy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DIY on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/diy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Shiitake Grow</title>
      <link>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>First thing I learned was that I migh have started the block to soon! The color was not a deep brown as I have read is the suggested color of the brick before starting fruiting.
Introduction Shiitake mushrooms, or Lentinula edodes, are a flavorful and nutritious edible mushroom from East Asia. Known for their savory taste and meaty texture, they are a popular choice in various cuisines.
Nutritional Benefits: Shiitakes are low in calories but rich in B-vitamins and minerals like zinc and iron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafting a CVG Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation</title>
      <link>/post/2024/rh223-cvg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/rh223-cvg/</guid>
      <description>Crafting a CVG Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation The Coir-Vermiculite-Gypsum (CVG) mixture is a cornerstone in the art of mushroom cultivation, celebrated for its remarkable ability to retain moisture and provide a nutrient-rich foundation. This guide delineates the process of creating a CVG substrate, integrating specific ingredients and measurements to yield optimal results.
Essential Ingredients and Their Costs Given the competitive pricing on Amazon, and considering the benefits of Prime membership, such as inclusive shipping, the following are the costs for the required materials:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
