<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>/docs/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 19:04:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Dear Readers,
Embark on a journey into the enchanting realm of mycology, a scientific discipline that unveils the mysteries of fungi, Earth&amp;rsquo;s often overlooked, yet profoundly influential organisms. As we extend a warm welcome to you, we invite you to explore the captivating world of mushrooms, molds, yeasts, and their intricate interactions with the ecosystems they inhabit.
Discover the Hidden Kingdom: Fungi constitute their own kingdom, separate from plants and animals, showcasing a diversity that is both astonishing and essential to life on our planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions (FAQ)</title>
      <link>/docs/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/faq/</guid>
      <description>General Questions Are you being paid by any of the companies that you have reviewed products for As of 2024-01-11 I have not been paid one penny and I have purchased all my products. If that every changes I will be sure to state that in future reviews.
Update 2024-01-24 I have joined the Amazon Associate program
Amazon Affiliate Disclaimer: &amp;ldquo;As an Amazon Associate, I earn from qualifying purchases. This video and description may contain affiliate links, which means that if you click on one of the product links, I’ll receive a small commission at no extra cost to you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RH223 Crypto Wallet Donations</title>
      <link>/docs/crypto-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/crypto-tips/</guid>
      <description>We love cryto! If you enjoy this content you can send a small tip to us, all we can give in return is a thank you and more great content.
RabbitHole223 Crypto Wallets ETH 0x602063b570AA01989E20F916b1B335790419cB9F
Bitcoin bc1qvrdzlffcpms97srlah8zyfq227ny5a3l2nt8eq
USD Coin 0x602063b570AA01989E20F916b1B335790419cB9F
Dogecoin DK4ya4jSACSrDnfxcVUeFzNrXYE5X6i64f
Litecoin LUiwuA9ag1PgzAa6RuYnULFcC1xfgtvooD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbithole223: Business Objectives 2024 Checkin Mile stone 1</title>
      <link>/post/2024/buisness-plan-2024-checkin-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/buisness-plan-2024-checkin-01/</guid>
      <description>May contain affiliate links, which means that if you click on one of the product links, I’ll receive a small commission at no extra cost to you. Key Objectives:
Reach 100 subscribers on YouTube by Feb 28th. Achived Feb 29th 2024) Initiate channel monetization and establish affiliate partnerships. Amazon Product Links Midwest Grow Kits Aspirants Analysis: UPDATED March 02, 2024 :
Renegade Mushrooms if you not watching his content you should be, this videos on monotub growth of culinary mushrooms has been amazing to see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Beginner&#39;s Mushroom Cultivation Journey: Part 2</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow-p2/</guid>
      <description>Not Legal Advice Disclaimer: The content provided herein is for informational purposes only and is not intended as legal advice. We accept no liability for any actions taken based on this information. Always consult local legislation and obtain legal counsel for guidance.
Recap In the initial installment of this series, we equipped a complete beginner with a grow bag and a spore syringe to begin an exciting venture into mushroom cultivation, focusing on the Golden Teacher strain, celebrated for its profound insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</guid>
      <description>Not Legal Advice Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice. The laws in Oregon, as with most places, are constantly changing, so do your own research and contact legal representation always.
Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights Oregon&amp;rsquo;s landmark decision to legalize psilocybin for therapeutic use under Measure 109 has set a precedent for psychedelic therapy in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Amateur Mushroom Grow Part 1</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/</guid>
      <description>Not Legal Advice Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.
Intro In this series, we send a total newbie a grow bag and a liquid culture syringe to embark on the captivating journey to explore the art of mushroom cultivation, specifically focusing on the Golden Teacher variety of mushrooms, known for its enlightening properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving into the World of Pioppino Mushrooms: A Culinary Adventure</title>
      <link>/post/2024/pioppino-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/pioppino-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>The Beginning of a Fungal Tale Imagine stumbling across a treasure chest, but instead of gold, it&amp;rsquo;s filled with spores! That&amp;rsquo;s what happened to me on Midwest Grow Kits, a haven for mycology enthusiasts that accepts Bitcoin—how futuristic! I grabbed their Mystery Kit Special, and what do I find? A Pioppino mushroom kit. Pioppino? Never heard of it, but I&amp;rsquo;m all in for a taste of the unknown. Wrapped up like a holiday gift, it sat waiting for its moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginner&#39;s Guide to Growing Mushrooms at Home Successfully</title>
      <link>/post/2024/beginners-guide-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/beginners-guide-part1/</guid>
      <description>2024-03-01 Update with Midwest Grow Kits Affilate links. Introduction Mushrooms have always fascinated me, and I&amp;rsquo;ve found joy in sharing this interest with others, especially those new to mushroom cultivation. Inspired by the informative and engaging content from creators like PhillyGoldenTeacher and therookiemycologist, I embarked on my own mushroom growing journey. Despite the challenges faced during my initial attempts, each failure was a step closer to understanding the delicate balance required for successful mushroom cultivation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pink Oyster Mushroom Maple &#39;Bacon&#39;: A Culinary Adventure</title>
      <link>/post/2024/pink-oyster-maple-bacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/pink-oyster-maple-bacon/</guid>
      <description>Yield: Four to six servings Hey everyone! Today, we&amp;rsquo;re diving into a fantastic cooking journey. We&amp;rsquo;re turning Pink Oyster mushrooms into an amazing &amp;lsquo;bacon&amp;rsquo; that&amp;rsquo;s not just easy to make, but also incredibly delicious. Trust me, your taste buds are in for a treat!
Ingredients 3 tablespoons butter (or vegan butter substitute) 3 tablespoons pure maple syrup 1 teaspoon smoked paprika 1 teaspoon garlic powder ¾ teaspoon salt ¼ teaspoon cracked black pepper 12 oz Pink Oyster mushrooms, cut into bacon-sized strips Let&amp;rsquo;s Get Cooking Step 1: Setting the Stage Alright, first up, let&amp;rsquo;s get that oven heated to 350°F (175°C).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rabbithole223: Business Objectives 2024</title>
      <link>/post/2024/buisness-plan-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/buisness-plan-2024/</guid>
      <description>Summary Rabbithole223 social media brand focused on mushroom growing and product reviews. We aim to enlighten and engage mushroom hobbyists and home growers. I am publishing this to be clear about my goals. Revenue is the focus for the first half of 2024. If we are successful in the next first few goals I will update with more. I really enjoy content from the To Dreams Of A Million youtube channel [To Dreams Of A Million] https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin for Colorado Readers</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</guid>
      <description>Not Legal Advice Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.
Overview In November 2022, Colorado voters passed Proposition 122 Legislative Council Draft, also known as the &amp;ldquo;Natural Medicine Health Act of 2022.&amp;rdquo; This groundbreaking legislation decriminalizes the possession, use, and personal cultivation of psychedelic mushrooms and other natural psychedelic substances for individuals aged 21 and over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Agar Agar cups for Amateur Mycologists: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Agar agar, a gelatinous substance derived from seaweed, is an essential tool for amateur mycologists. Its unique properties make it an ideal medium for cultivating fungi. This article provides a detailed, step-by-step guide on how to make agar agar at home using a simple recipe that combines potato flakes, agar agar, and light corn syrup.
Huge thank you to PhillyGoldenTeacher and therookiemycologist for their content. The recipe below is from PhillyGoldenTeachers agar video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Shiitake Grow</title>
      <link>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>2024-03-01 Update with Midwest Grow Kits Affilate links. First thing I learned was that I might have started the block too soon! The color was not as deep brown as I have read is the suggested color of the brick before starting fruiting.
Introduction Shiitake mushrooms, or Lentinula edodes, are flavorful and nutritious edible mushrooms from East Asia. Known for their savory taste and meaty texture, they are a popular choice in various cuisines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Mycelium: The Hidden Power Beneath Our Feet</title>
      <link>/post/2024/understanding-mycelium/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/understanding-mycelium/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Imagine a world beneath our feet, intricate and vital, yet unseen. This is the world of mycelium, a fundamental component of our ecosystems. Often overlooked, mycelium is a key player in nature&amp;rsquo;s cycle. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore this fascinating network that lies under the soil.
What is Mycelium? Mycelium is essentially the foundation of the fungi kingdom, much like roots are to plants. These thread-like structures, known as hyphae, weave together to form a complex and expansive web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafting a CVG Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation</title>
      <link>/post/2024/rh223-cvg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/rh223-cvg/</guid>
      <description>Crafting a CVG Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation The Coir-Vermiculite-Gypsum (CVG) mixture is a cornerstone in the art of mushroom cultivation, celebrated for its remarkable ability to retain moisture and provide a nutrient-rich foundation. This guide delineates the process of creating a CVG substrate, integrating specific ingredients and measurements to yield optimal results.
Essential Ingredients and Their Costs Given the competitive pricing on Amazon, and considering the benefits of Prime membership, such as inclusive shipping, the following are the costs for the required materials:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coco Coir Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation: An In-Depth Price Comparison</title>
      <link>/post/2024/buying-coco-coir-blocks-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/buying-coco-coir-blocks-blocks/</guid>
      <description>Coco Coir Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation: An In-Depth Price Comparison Introduction Coco coir, increasingly recognized as an effective substrate for mushroom cultivation, is valued for its moisture retention, pH neutrality, and facilitation of mycelial growth. This guide offers a thorough comparison of coco coir products, focusing on both cost-effectiveness and their appropriateness for different mushroom growing scales.
Why Coco Coir? Coco coir, a by-product of coconut fiber processing, is known for its excellent water retention, essential for mushroom cultivation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of Lion&#39;s Mane Mushroom Growing Kit from North Spore</title>
      <link>/post/2024/northspore-lions-mane-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/northspore-lions-mane-kit/</guid>
      <description>2024-03-01 Update with Midwest Grow Kits Affilate links. Introduction Recently, I embarked on a fascinating journey of mushroom cultivation by purchasing the Lion&amp;rsquo;s Mane Mushroom Growing Kit from North Spore.
First Impressions Upon arrival, I found the kit contained everything necessary for a novice grower to start immediately. The clarity of the instructions was exceptional, simplifying the setup process. The included spray bottle was perfect for a first-time mushroom grower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing the Power of UV-C Light in Amateur Mycology</title>
      <link>/post/2024/uvc-handheld-lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/uvc-handheld-lights/</guid>
      <description>2024-03-01 Update with Midwest Grow Kits Affilate links. WARNING: While UV-C light offers a non-chemical, no-touch sterilization method, its use requires careful handling: Safety Precautions: Always use protective gear, like gloves and safety goggles, to minimize skin and eye exposure. Controlled Usage: Limit the duration and frequency of UV-C light exposure to skin to reduce potential health risks. Educate Yourself: Understand the implications of UV-C light use, including the potential cancer risk, and follow guidelines for safe operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myco Labs Grower&#39;s Select Mushroom 48-Quart Monotub Fruiting Chamber with Filter Disks and Liner</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mycolabs-growers-select-monotub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/mycolabs-growers-select-monotub/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The 48-Quart Monotub from Myco Labs was my first monotub. This kit is nice, but I do have a few concerns.
Ordering and Assembly Ordered from Amazon, and it arrived promptly as usual. When it arrived, I had a look and was faced with a decision: to put the plugs in or the filters over the holes. Since I was using a North Spore Organic Lion&amp;rsquo;s Mane Mushroom Spray &amp;amp; Grow Kit, which was already starting to fruit, and I just needed to control moisture levels, I chose to use half the plugs and leave the other holes open, considering that while fruiting, there is not as much risk of contamination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPDATED: Hydroponic Humidifier System Review: A Cultivator&#39;s Perspective</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton-updated/</guid>
      <description>Introduction OK on my first run with the Hydroponic Humidifier System with HEPA Air Hoses I didnt have a lot of luck. As expected it was moslty user error. I am not going to cover the product details here again but you can ready my orginal review CLICK HERE and get all that fun info.
Initial Expectations To restate my orginal expections, With the system running on a schedule of 1 hour on and 5 hours off, I anticipated a the least a mild improvement in humidity levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the BoomRoom II: A Sneak Peek into Northspore&#39;s Automated Martha Tent Mushroom Grow Kit</title>
      <link>/post/2024/boomroomii-prerelease/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/boomroomii-prerelease/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Home mushroom cultivation enthusiasts, gear up for an exciting addition to your mycology projects – Northspore&amp;rsquo;s upcoming release, the BoomRoom II Automated Martha Tent Mushroom Grow Kit. In this pre-review article, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the key features that make this kit stand out and explore how it could elevate your mushroom cultivation game.
The Allure of the BoomRoom II Northspore is set to launch the BoomRoom II, a comprehensive solution for at-home mushroom cultivation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydroponic Humidifier System Review: A Cultivator&#39;s Perspective</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 02:57:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As an mushroom cultivator, I recently invested in a Hydroponic Humidifier System designed explicitly for maintaining optimal humidity levels during the growth process. Excited about the potential improvements in my monotub cultivation, I aimed to cotrol the humidity control for a more efficient and productive mushroom-growing environment for my Lions Mane mushroom kit from North Spore.
Product Details The hydroponic humidifier system includes essential components for a comprehensive setup:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Review of the Midwest Grow Kits Mushroom Ecosphere 3.0</title>
      <link>/post/2024/ecosphere3-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/ecosphere3-base/</guid>
      <description>2024-03-01 Update with Midwest Grow Kits Affilate links. Introduction Embarking on a journey into home mushroom cultivation, we opted for the Mushroom Ecosphere 3.0 from Midwest Grow Kits. Our experience with this system has been a mix of highs and lows, and here we are offering insights into its assembly, additional accessories, and functionality.
Ordering and Assembly The initial process of purchasing the Mushroom Ecosphere 3.0 was straightforward and efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mushroom Atrium Project</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mushroom-atrium-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 22:57:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/mushroom-atrium-project/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A simple Mushroom Atrium I saw on youtube and am trying to reproduce.
Intro Video Supplies List Kitchen Dish Rack $14.00 https://share.temu.com/gxinTM5kp6A
DC5V WS2812B 5m/Roll 60/m Black/White PCB IP65 $6 https://a.aliexpress.com/_mMrDBze</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 19:04:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
