<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Northspore on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/northspore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Northspore on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/northspore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review of Lion&#39;s Mane Mushroom Growing Kit from North Spore</title>
      <link>/post/2024/northspore-lions-mane-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/northspore-lions-mane-kit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024-03-01 Update with &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Midwest Grow Kits&lt;/a&gt; Affilate links.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I embarked on a fascinating journey of mushroom cultivation by purchasing the &lt;strong&gt;Lion&amp;rsquo;s Mane Mushroom Growing Kit&lt;/strong&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;https://northspore.com/collections/beginner-kits/products/grow-your-own-lions-mane&#34;&gt;North Spore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-impressions&#34;&gt;First Impressions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upon arrival, I found the kit contained everything necessary for a novice grower to start immediately. The &lt;strong&gt;clarity of the instructions&lt;/strong&gt; was exceptional, simplifying the setup process. The included spray bottle was perfect for a first-time mushroom grower.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;quality-and-experience&#34;&gt;Quality and Experience&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;substrate-and-mycelium-health&#34;&gt;Substrate and Mycelium Health&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;quality of the substrate&lt;/strong&gt; and the health of the mycelium were impressive. These factors almost guaranteed a successful and bountiful growth. The block was almost solid white, and it was clear it was ready for fruiting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the BoomRoom II: A Sneak Peek into Northspore&#39;s Automated Martha Tent Mushroom Grow Kit</title>
      <link>/post/2024/boomroomii-prerelease/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/boomroomii-prerelease/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Home mushroom cultivation enthusiasts, gear up for an exciting addition to your mycology projects – Northspore&amp;rsquo;s upcoming release, the BoomRoom II Automated Martha Tent Mushroom Grow Kit. In this pre-review article, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the key features that make this kit stand out and explore how it could elevate your mushroom cultivation game.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-allure-of-the-boomroom-ii&#34;&gt;The Allure of the BoomRoom II&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Northspore is set to launch the BoomRoom II, a comprehensive solution for at-home mushroom cultivation. One of the standout features is the default 5 shelf tent, offering a whopping 18 cubic ft. of growing space. This design promises to allow cultivators to grow up to 9 times more mushrooms than with traditional monotubs, making it an appealing option for those looking to maximize their yields.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
