<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beginners Guide on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/beginners-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beginners Guide on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/beginners-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Growing Golden Teacher Mushrooms</title>
      <link>/post/2025/growing-gteachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/growing-gteachers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;growing-golden-teacher-mushrooms&#34;&gt;Growing Golden Teacher Mushrooms&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Golden Teacher mushrooms have become popular among home growers thanks to their relatively easy cultivation process and distinctive golden caps. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to grow these fascinating fungi at home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-youll-need&#34;&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Golden Teacher mushrooms require a few basic supplies to get started. You&amp;rsquo;ll need a substrate (growing medium), spores or spawn, containers, and basic equipment to maintain proper growing conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-by-step-growing-process&#34;&gt;Step-by-Step Growing Process&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, prepare your substrate. Many growers use a mixture of brown rice flour and vermiculite, which provides nutrients and proper moisture retention. Mix these ingredients with water, then fill small containers about two-thirds full.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Does It Cost to Start Growing Mushrooms?</title>
      <link>/post/2024/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting your journey into mushroom cultivation can be both exciting and cost-effective. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a hobbyist looking to grow a few mushrooms for personal use or someone aiming to dive into a more serious cultivation setup, understanding the initial investment is crucial. Here, we&amp;rsquo;ll break down the costs and provide insights into what you can expect when setting up your own mushroom growing operation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started-with-a-grow-kit&#34;&gt;Getting Started with a Grow Kit&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those who are new to mushroom growing, a grow kit is a fantastic way to start. These kits are user-friendly and come with everything you need to grow your first batch of mushrooms. Prices for grow kits typically start at around $30. You can find reliable kits &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/SimpleKit&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Using this referral link helps support us at no extra cost to you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
