<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>diy on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/diy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in diy on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/diy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Affiliate Links</title>
      <link>/docs/affiliate-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/affiliate-links/</guid>
      <description>Contains affiliate links, which means that if you click on one of the product links, I’ll receive a small commission at no extra cost to you. Amazon Midwest Grow Kits TubeBuddy Products purchases from online vendors for videos Echosphere 3.0 kit Spawn Media BEN&amp;rsquo;S ORIGINAL Ready Rice Whole Grain Brown Rice Pouch (Pack of 12) 100% Organic Rye Berries 5lb Bulk Organic Rye Berries (40 LBS) Premium 5-Grain Spawn Bags 3-Pack Premium 24 Oz Super-Quick-Colonizing 5-grain Jar (24oz) Substrate Media (Hay, Wood Pelets, Perlite, Coco ) Compressed Organic Coco Coir Brick 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving into the World of Pioppino Mushrooms: A Culinary Adventure</title>
      <link>/post/2024/pioppino-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/pioppino-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>The Beginning of a Fungal Tale Imagine stumbling across a treasure chest, but instead of gold, it&amp;rsquo;s filled with spores! That&amp;rsquo;s what happened to me on Midwest Grow Kits, a haven for mycology enthusiasts that accepts Bitcoin—how futuristic! I grabbed their Mystery Kit Special, and what do I find? A Pioppino mushroom kit. Pioppino? Never heard of it, but I&amp;rsquo;m all in for a taste of the unknown. Wrapped up like a holiday gift, it sat waiting for its moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Agar Agar cups for Amateur Mycologists: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Agar agar, a gelatinous substance derived from seaweed, is an essential tool for amateur mycologists. Its unique properties make it an ideal medium for cultivating fungi. This article provides a detailed, step-by-step guide on how to make agar agar at home using a simple recipe that combines potato flakes, agar agar, and light corn syrup.
Huge thank you to PhillyGoldenTeacher and therookiemycologist for their content. The recipe below is from PhillyGoldenTeachers agar video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Shiitake Grow</title>
      <link>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>2024-03-01 Update with Midwest Grow Kits Affilate links. First thing I learned was that I might have started the block too soon! The color was not as deep brown as I have read is the suggested color of the brick before starting fruiting.
Introduction Shiitake mushrooms, or Lentinula edodes, are flavorful and nutritious edible mushrooms from East Asia. Known for their savory taste and meaty texture, they are a popular choice in various cuisines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mushroom Atrium Project</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mushroom-atrium-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 22:57:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/mushroom-atrium-project/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A simple Mushroom Atrium I saw on youtube and am trying to reproduce.
Intro Video Supplies List Kitchen Dish Rack $14.00 https://share.temu.com/gxinTM5kp6A
DC5V WS2812B 5m/Roll 60/m Black/White PCB IP65 $6 https://a.aliexpress.com/_mMrDBze</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
