<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>diy on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/diy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in diy on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/diy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Make Agar Agar cups for Amateur Mycologists: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Agar agar, a gelatinous substance derived from seaweed, is an essential tool for amateur mycologists. Its unique properties make it an ideal medium for cultivating fungi. This article provides a detailed, step-by-step guide on how to make agar agar at home using a simple recipe that combines potato flakes, agar agar, and light corn syrup.
Huge thank you to PhillyGoldenTeacher and therookiemycologist for their content. The recipe below is from PhillyGoldenTeachers agar video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Shiitake Grow</title>
      <link>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>First thing I learned was that I might have started the block too soon! The color was not as deep brown as I have read is the suggested color of the brick before starting fruiting.
Introduction Shiitake mushrooms, or Lentinula edodes, are flavorful and nutritious edible mushrooms from East Asia. Known for their savory taste and meaty texture, they are a popular choice in various cuisines.
My personal motivation for choosing to grow shiitake mushrooms stemmed from a desire to embark on a new learning journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mushroom Atrium Project</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mushroom-atrium-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 22:57:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/mushroom-atrium-project/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A simple Mushroom Atrium I saw on youtube and am trying to reproduce.
Intro Video Supplies List Kitchen Dish Rack $14.00 https://share.temu.com/gxinTM5kp6A
DC5V WS2812B 5m/Roll 60/m Black/White PCB IP65 $6 https://a.aliexpress.com/_mMrDBze</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
