<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mushroom Cultivation on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/mushroom-cultivation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mushroom Cultivation on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/mushroom-cultivation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are Mushroom Grow Bag Guarantees Real? My Zombie MyCo Experience</title>
      <link>/post/2025/zombie-bag-replacement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/zombie-bag-replacement/</guid>
      <description>After initial mushroom grow bags from Zombie MyCo failed to colonize, customer support promptly sent replacements, proving their bag guarantee is genuine and reliable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Growing Golden Teacher Mushrooms</title>
      <link>/post/2025/growing-gteachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/growing-gteachers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;growing-golden-teacher-mushrooms&#34;&gt;Growing Golden Teacher Mushrooms&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Golden Teacher mushrooms have become popular among home growers thanks to their relatively easy cultivation process and distinctive golden caps. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to grow these fascinating fungi at home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-youll-need&#34;&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Growing Golden Teacher can be easy or hard, given your likely just learning lets do it the easy way. Get your self a all in one grow bag, personally I have been using &lt;a href=&#34;https://zombiemyco.com&#34;&gt;zombiemyco.com&lt;/a&gt; grow bags and have had good results. More importantly the one issue I did have they made it right. Lots of companies say they stand by their product it seems Zombie actually does. This bag &lt;a href=&#34;https://zombiemyco.com/products/mushroom-grow-bag-5lb&#34;&gt;5lb Grow bag&lt;/a&gt; is perfect for starting out. I am no affiliated with the at all as of March 02, 2025, maybe if you mention me in your purchase they can change that. Next you need some liquid culture, sure you can do spores but don&amp;rsquo;t just don&amp;rsquo;t for your first try. Its been a long time since I have actually purchases any liquid culture so I can not really suggesting anyone at this time. If you really want to go with spores I highly suggest &lt;a href=&#34;https://inoculatetheworld.com/product/golden-teacher-isolated-syringe/&#34;&gt;inoculatetheworld&lt;/a&gt; another company who I know stands behind their products.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trials and Tribulations of Growing Mushrooms: A Story of Setbacks and Perseverance</title>
      <link>/post/2024/trials-tribulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/trials-tribulations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-trials-and-tribulations-of-growing-mushrooms-a-story-of-setbacks-and-perseverance&#34;&gt;The Trials and Tribulations of Growing Mushrooms: A Story of Setbacks and Perseverance&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hey there, my fellow fungi enthusiasts! Today, I want to share a personal story about my mushroom growing journey. It&amp;rsquo;s not all sunshine and rainbows – there have been plenty of bumps along the way. From battling bacteria to dealing with video censorship on YouTube, I&amp;rsquo;ve faced my fair share of challenges. But through it all, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned some valuable lessons about resilience and finding my way back on the path.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Beginner&#39;s Mushroom Cultivation Journey: Part 2</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: The content provided herein is for informational purposes only and is not intended as legal advice. We accept no liability for any actions taken based on this information. Always consult local legislation and obtain legal counsel for guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;recap&#34;&gt;Recap&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&#34;/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/&#34;&gt;initial installment&lt;/a&gt; of this series, we equipped a complete beginner with a grow bag and a spore syringe to begin an exciting venture into mushroom cultivation, focusing on the Golden Teacher strain, celebrated for its profound insights. We procured a user-friendly all-in-one grow bag and a Golden Teacher spore syringe from a reputable supplier to kickstart this journey.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice. The laws in Oregon, as with most places, are constantly changing, so do your own research and contact legal representation always.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;oregon-psilocybin-2024-update-navigating-new-mushroom-laws-and-program-insights&#34;&gt;Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oregon&amp;rsquo;s landmark decision to legalize psilocybin for therapeutic use under Measure 109 has set a precedent for psychedelic therapy in the United States. As we navigate through 2024, significant updates to Oregon&amp;rsquo;s mushroom laws have unfolded, presenting both advancements and challenges in the program&amp;rsquo;s implementation. We are highly disturbed by the lack of inclusion of the right for small batch personal usage home growth and ask who stands to benefit most! As usual, big money is running the show, and you will need to have deep pockets to play.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Amateur Mushroom Grow Part 1</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this series, we send a total newbie a grow bag and a liquid culture syringe to embark on the captivating journey to explore the art of mushroom cultivation, specifically focusing on the Golden Teacher variety of mushrooms, known for its enlightening properties. We&amp;rsquo;ve order  an all-in-one grow bag and a liquid culture syringe from a known vendor to get started.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving into the World of Pioppino Mushrooms: A Culinary Adventure</title>
      <link>/post/2024/pioppino-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/pioppino-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mP_jcvbVTP4?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-beginning-of-a-fungal-tale&#34;&gt;The Beginning of a Fungal Tale&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine stumbling across a treasure chest, but instead of gold, it&amp;rsquo;s filled with spores! That&amp;rsquo;s what happened to me on Midwest Grow Kits, a haven for mycology enthusiasts that accepts Bitcoin—how futuristic! I grabbed their &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/ReadyGrow&#34;&gt;Mystery Kit Special&lt;/a&gt;, and what do I find? A Pioppino mushroom kit. Pioppino? Never heard of it, but I&amp;rsquo;m all in for a taste of the unknown. Wrapped up like a holiday gift, it sat waiting for its moment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin for Colorado Readers</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In November 2022, Colorado voters passed Proposition 122 &lt;a href=&#34;https://leg.colorado.gov/sites/default/files/initiative%2520referendum_proposition%20122%20final%20lc%20packet.pdf&#34;&gt;Legislative Council Draft&lt;/a&gt;, also known as the &amp;ldquo;Natural Medicine Health Act of 2022.&amp;rdquo; This groundbreaking legislation decriminalizes the possession, use, and personal cultivation of psychedelic mushrooms and other natural psychedelic substances for individuals aged 21 and over.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Agar Agar cups for Amateur Mycologists: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups-copy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/F0z-LwC_qNo?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Agar agar, a gelatinous substance derived from seaweed, is an essential tool for amateur mycologists. Its unique properties make it an ideal medium for cultivating fungi. This article provides a detailed, step-by-step guide on how to make agar agar at home using a simple recipe that combines potato flakes, agar agar, and light corn syrup.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Shiitake Grow</title>
      <link>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024-03-01 Update with &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Midwest Grow Kits&lt;/a&gt; Affilate links.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First thing I learned was that I might have started the block too soon! The color was not as deep brown as I have read is the suggested color of the brick before starting fruiting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shiitake mushrooms, or Lentinula edodes, are flavorful and nutritious edible mushrooms from East Asia. Known for their savory taste and meaty texture, they are a popular choice in various cuisines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting a CVG Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation</title>
      <link>/post/2024/rh223-cvg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/rh223-cvg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/MPUW306ZoLg?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;crafting-a-cvg-substrate-for-mushroom-cultivation&#34;&gt;Crafting a CVG Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Coir-Vermiculite-Gypsum (CVG) mixture is a cornerstone in the art of mushroom cultivation, celebrated for its remarkable ability to retain moisture and provide a nutrient-rich foundation. This guide delineates the process of creating a CVG substrate, integrating specific ingredients and measurements to yield optimal results.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
