<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mushroom cultivation on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/mushroom-cultivation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mushroom cultivation on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/mushroom-cultivation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Diving into the World of Pioppino Mushrooms: A Culinary Adventure</title>
      <link>/post/2024/pioppino-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/pioppino-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>The Beginning of a Fungal Tale Imagine stumbling across a treasure chest, but instead of gold, it&amp;rsquo;s filled with spores! That&amp;rsquo;s what happened to me on Midwest Grow Kits, a haven for mycology enthusiasts that accepts Bitcoin—how futuristic! I grabbed their Mystery Kit Special, and what do I find? A Pioppino mushroom kit. Pioppino? Never heard of it, but I&amp;rsquo;m all in for a taste of the unknown. Wrapped up like a holiday gift, it sat waiting for its moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin for Colorado Readers</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</guid>
      <description>Not Legal Advice Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.
Overview In November 2022, Colorado voters passed Proposition 122 Legislative Council Draft, also known as the &amp;ldquo;Natural Medicine Health Act of 2022.&amp;rdquo; This groundbreaking legislation decriminalizes the possession, use, and personal cultivation of psychedelic mushrooms and other natural psychedelic substances for individuals aged 21 and over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Agar Agar cups for Amateur Mycologists: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/agar-ketchup-cups/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Agar agar, a gelatinous substance derived from seaweed, is an essential tool for amateur mycologists. Its unique properties make it an ideal medium for cultivating fungi. This article provides a detailed, step-by-step guide on how to make agar agar at home using a simple recipe that combines potato flakes, agar agar, and light corn syrup.
Huge thank you to PhillyGoldenTeacher and therookiemycologist for their content. The recipe below is from PhillyGoldenTeachers agar video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Shiitake Grow</title>
      <link>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/shiitake-grow-2024/</guid>
      <description>First thing I learned was that I might have started the block too soon! The color was not as deep brown as I have read is the suggested color of the brick before starting fruiting.
Introduction Shiitake mushrooms, or Lentinula edodes, are flavorful and nutritious edible mushrooms from East Asia. Known for their savory taste and meaty texture, they are a popular choice in various cuisines.
My personal motivation for choosing to grow shiitake mushrooms stemmed from a desire to embark on a new learning journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crafting a CVG Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation</title>
      <link>/post/2024/rh223-cvg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2024/rh223-cvg/</guid>
      <description>Crafting a CVG Substrate for Mushroom Cultivation The Coir-Vermiculite-Gypsum (CVG) mixture is a cornerstone in the art of mushroom cultivation, celebrated for its remarkable ability to retain moisture and provide a nutrient-rich foundation. This guide delineates the process of creating a CVG substrate, integrating specific ingredients and measurements to yield optimal results.
Essential Ingredients and Their Costs Given the competitive pricing on Amazon, and considering the benefits of Prime membership, such as inclusive shipping, the following are the costs for the required materials:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
