<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mycology on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/categories/mycology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mycology on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/mycology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Critical Relationship Between Mycelium Growth and Temperature</title>
      <link>/post/2025/growth-and-temperature/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/growth-and-temperature/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Temperature serves as the primary regulator of mycelium development in fungi cultivation. This relationship between thermal conditions and fungal growth represents one of the most significant yet frequently underestimated variables affecting cultivation success. My experiences with temperature management have demonstrated that even minor fluctuations can dramatically alter colonization rates, yield potential, and contamination risks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;temperature-thresholds-and-metabolic-functions&#34;&gt;Temperature Thresholds and Metabolic Functions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mycelium growth demonstrates distinct temperature thresholds that directly influence metabolic function. Most cubensis varieties require temperatures between 75-80°F (24-27°C) for optimal colonization. Below 70°F (21°C), enzymatic activity diminishes considerably, causing growth to decelerate or halt entirely. Temperatures exceeding 86°F (30°C) create conditions that favor bacterial proliferation, often resulting in contamination that renders substrates unusable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penis Envy Mushrooms: Understanding a Potent Psilocybin Variety</title>
      <link>/post/2025/penis-envy-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/penis-envy-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;penis-envy-mushrooms-understanding-a-potent-psilocybin-variety&#34;&gt;Penis Envy Mushrooms: Understanding a Potent Psilocybin Variety&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Penis Envy mushrooms represent one of the most recognizable and potent varieties of psilocybin-containing fungi in the world. Despite their somewhat provocative name, these mushrooms have earned significant attention in mycological communities for their unique appearance, potency, and the scientific questions they raise. This article explores their history, characteristics, and place in modern ethnobotanical research.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;origins-and-discovery&#34;&gt;Origins and Discovery&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The origin story of Penis Envy mushrooms is intertwined with notable figures in psychedelic culture. According to mycological lore, renowned ethnomycologist Terence McKenna discovered the original specimen in the Amazon rainforest during the early 1970s. He allegedly sent spores to colleagues, including mycologist Steven Pollock, who further cultivated and refined the strain. Through selective isolation, the distinctive characteristics we now associate with Penis Envy mushrooms became stabilized.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
