<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mushrooms on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/mushrooms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mushrooms on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/mushrooms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Ecosphere 3.0</title>
      <link>/post/2025/goodbye-ecosphere3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/goodbye-ecosphere3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;goodbye-ecosphere-30&#34;&gt;Goodbye Ecosphere 3.0&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re serious about indoor growing, picking the right grow tent system is key to creating a controlled and efficient environment.  I started with the Ecosphere 3.0 from Midwest Grow Kit and it seemed good but over time it became clear it a was not a good fit. The plastic cover was very fragile and I was it separated at were the zipper connected to the plastic. On the third time replacing the cover I was fed up. The wire racks also turned out to be flimsy and a pain to deal with with the fragile plastic grow tent cover of the Ecosphere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penis Envy Mushrooms: Understanding a Potent Psilocybin Variety</title>
      <link>/post/2025/penis-envy-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/penis-envy-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;penis-envy-mushrooms-understanding-a-potent-psilocybin-variety&#34;&gt;Penis Envy Mushrooms: Understanding a Potent Psilocybin Variety&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Penis Envy mushrooms represent one of the most recognizable and potent varieties of psilocybin-containing fungi in the world. Despite their somewhat provocative name, these mushrooms have earned significant attention in mycological communities for their unique appearance, potency, and the scientific questions they raise. This article explores their history, characteristics, and place in modern ethnobotanical research.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;origins-and-discovery&#34;&gt;Origins and Discovery&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The origin story of Penis Envy mushrooms is intertwined with notable figures in psychedelic culture. According to mycological lore, renowned ethnomycologist Terence McKenna discovered the original specimen in the Amazon rainforest during the early 1970s. He allegedly sent spores to colleagues, including mycologist Steven Pollock, who further cultivated and refined the strain. Through selective isolation, the distinctive characteristics we now associate with Penis Envy mushrooms became stabilized.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of Lion&#39;s Mane Mushroom Growing Kit from North Spore</title>
      <link>/post/2024/northspore-lions-mane-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/northspore-lions-mane-kit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024-03-01 Update with &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Midwest Grow Kits&lt;/a&gt; Affilate links.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I embarked on a fascinating journey of mushroom cultivation by purchasing the &lt;strong&gt;Lion&amp;rsquo;s Mane Mushroom Growing Kit&lt;/strong&gt; from &lt;a href=&#34;https://northspore.com/collections/beginner-kits/products/grow-your-own-lions-mane&#34;&gt;North Spore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-impressions&#34;&gt;First Impressions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upon arrival, I found the kit contained everything necessary for a novice grower to start immediately. The &lt;strong&gt;clarity of the instructions&lt;/strong&gt; was exceptional, simplifying the setup process. The included spray bottle was perfect for a first-time mushroom grower.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;quality-and-experience&#34;&gt;Quality and Experience&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;substrate-and-mycelium-health&#34;&gt;Substrate and Mycelium Health&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;quality of the substrate&lt;/strong&gt; and the health of the mycelium were impressive. These factors almost guaranteed a successful and bountiful growth. The block was almost solid white, and it was clear it was ready for fruiting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myco Labs Grower&#39;s Select Mushroom 48-Quart Monotub Fruiting Chamber with Filter Disks and Liner</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mycolabs-growers-select-monotub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/mycolabs-growers-select-monotub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://amzn.to/3UmBLyY&#34;&gt;48-Quart Monotub&lt;/a&gt; from Myco Labs was my first monotub. This kit is nice, but I do have a few concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;ordering-and-assembly&#34;&gt;Ordering and Assembly&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ordered from Amazon, and it arrived promptly as usual. When it arrived, I had a look and was faced with a decision: to put the plugs in or the filters over the holes. Since I was using a &lt;a href=&#34;https://amzn.to/3Oo3zyU&#34;&gt;North Spore Organic Lion&amp;rsquo;s Mane Mushroom Spray &amp;amp; Grow Kit&lt;/a&gt;, which was already starting to fruit, and I just needed to control moisture levels, I chose to use half the plugs and leave the other holes open, considering that while fruiting, there is not as much risk of contamination.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATED: Hydroponic Humidifier System Review: A Cultivator&#39;s Perspective</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton-updated/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OK on my first run with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Hydroponic Humidifier System with HEPA Air Hoses&lt;/a&gt; I didnt have a lot of luck. As expected it was moslty user error. I am not going to cover the product details here again but you can ready my orginal review &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rabbithole223.com/post/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton/&#34;&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt; and get all that fun info.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;initial-expectations&#34;&gt;Initial Expectations&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To restate my orginal expections, With the system running on a schedule of 1 hour on and 5 hours off, I anticipated a the least a mild improvement in humidity levels. I figured I would have to adjust the amount of time on / off, soi this was just a starting point.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the BoomRoom II: A Sneak Peek into Northspore&#39;s Automated Martha Tent Mushroom Grow Kit</title>
      <link>/post/2024/boomroomii-prerelease/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/boomroomii-prerelease/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Home mushroom cultivation enthusiasts, gear up for an exciting addition to your mycology projects – Northspore&amp;rsquo;s upcoming release, the BoomRoom II Automated Martha Tent Mushroom Grow Kit. In this pre-review article, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the key features that make this kit stand out and explore how it could elevate your mushroom cultivation game.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-allure-of-the-boomroom-ii&#34;&gt;The Allure of the BoomRoom II&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Northspore is set to launch the BoomRoom II, a comprehensive solution for at-home mushroom cultivation. One of the standout features is the default 5 shelf tent, offering a whopping 18 cubic ft. of growing space. This design promises to allow cultivators to grow up to 9 times more mushrooms than with traditional monotubs, making it an appealing option for those looking to maximize their yields.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hydroponic Humidifier System Review: A Cultivator&#39;s Perspective</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 02:57:38 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/mwgk-hydroponichumidifier-hydroton/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an mushroom cultivator, I recently invested in a &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Hydroponic Humidifier System&lt;/a&gt; designed explicitly for maintaining optimal humidity levels during the growth process. Excited about the potential improvements in my monotub cultivation, I aimed to cotrol the humidity control for a more efficient and productive mushroom-growing environment for my Lions Mane mushroom kit from North Spore.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;product-details&#34;&gt;Product Details&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The hydroponic humidifier system includes essential components for a comprehensive setup:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aqua-Air Pro 2.5w High Power Air Pump:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Review of the Midwest Grow Kits Mushroom Ecosphere 3.0</title>
      <link>/post/2024/ecosphere3-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/ecosphere3-base/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024-03-01 Update with &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Midwest Grow Kits&lt;/a&gt; Affilate links.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Embarking on a journey into home mushroom cultivation, we opted for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/Ecosphere&#34;&gt;Mushroom Ecosphere 3.0&lt;/a&gt; from Midwest Grow Kits. Our experience with this system has been a mix of highs and lows, and here we are offering insights into its assembly, additional accessories, and functionality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;ordering-and-assembly&#34;&gt;Ordering and Assembly&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The initial process of purchasing the Mushroom Ecosphere 3.0 was straightforward and efficient. The package arrived promptly, and the assembly was relatively easy. We opted to enhance the system with the addition of the 5th shelf, a decision that later proved to be a mixed bag.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mushroom Atrium Project</title>
      <link>/post/2024/mushroom-atrium-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 22:57:38 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/mushroom-atrium-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A simple Mushroom Atrium I saw on youtube and am trying to reproduce.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;intro-video&#34;&gt;Intro Video&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wtLj63XPd3A?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;supplies-list&#34;&gt;Supplies List&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kitchen Dish Rack $14.00&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://share.temu.com/gxinTM5kp6A&#34;&gt;https://share.temu.com/gxinTM5kp6A&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DC5V WS2812B 5m/Roll 60/m Black/White PCB IP65 $6&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://a.aliexpress.com/_mMrDBze&#34;&gt;https://a.aliexpress.com/_mMrDBze&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
