<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MAGIC-QUADRANT on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/categories/magic-quadrant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MAGIC-QUADRANT on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/magic-quadrant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Growing Golden Teacher Mushrooms</title>
      <link>/post/2025/growing-gteachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/growing-gteachers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;growing-golden-teacher-mushrooms&#34;&gt;Growing Golden Teacher Mushrooms&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Golden Teacher mushrooms have become popular among home growers thanks to their relatively easy cultivation process and distinctive golden caps. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to grow these fascinating fungi at home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-youll-need&#34;&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Golden Teacher mushrooms require a few basic supplies to get started. You&amp;rsquo;ll need a substrate (growing medium), spores or spawn, containers, and basic equipment to maintain proper growing conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;step-by-step-growing-process&#34;&gt;Step-by-Step Growing Process&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, prepare your substrate. Many growers use a mixture of brown rice flour and vermiculite, which provides nutrients and proper moisture retention. Mix these ingredients with water, then fill small containers about two-thirds full.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Beginner&#39;s Mushroom Cultivation Journey: Part 2</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: The content provided herein is for informational purposes only and is not intended as legal advice. We accept no liability for any actions taken based on this information. Always consult local legislation and obtain legal counsel for guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;recap&#34;&gt;Recap&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&#34;/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/&#34;&gt;initial installment&lt;/a&gt; of this series, we equipped a complete beginner with a grow bag and a spore syringe to begin an exciting venture into mushroom cultivation, focusing on the Golden Teacher strain, celebrated for its profound insights. We procured a user-friendly all-in-one grow bag and a Golden Teacher spore syringe from a reputable supplier to kickstart this journey.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice. The laws in Oregon, as with most places, are constantly changing, so do your own research and contact legal representation always.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;oregon-psilocybin-2024-update-navigating-new-mushroom-laws-and-program-insights&#34;&gt;Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oregon&amp;rsquo;s landmark decision to legalize psilocybin for therapeutic use under Measure 109 has set a precedent for psychedelic therapy in the United States. As we navigate through 2024, significant updates to Oregon&amp;rsquo;s mushroom laws have unfolded, presenting both advancements and challenges in the program&amp;rsquo;s implementation. We are highly disturbed by the lack of inclusion of the right for small batch personal usage home growth and ask who stands to benefit most! As usual, big money is running the show, and you will need to have deep pockets to play.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Amateur Mushroom Grow Part 1</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this series, we send a total newbie a grow bag and a liquid culture syringe to embark on the captivating journey to explore the art of mushroom cultivation, specifically focusing on the Golden Teacher variety of mushrooms, known for its enlightening properties. We&amp;rsquo;ve order  an all-in-one grow bag and a liquid culture syringe from a known vendor to get started.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin for Colorado Readers</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;not-legal-advice&#34;&gt;Not Legal Advice&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In November 2022, Colorado voters passed Proposition 122 &lt;a href=&#34;https://leg.colorado.gov/sites/default/files/initiative%2520referendum_proposition%20122%20final%20lc%20packet.pdf&#34;&gt;Legislative Council Draft&lt;/a&gt;, also known as the &amp;ldquo;Natural Medicine Health Act of 2022.&amp;rdquo; This groundbreaking legislation decriminalizes the possession, use, and personal cultivation of psychedelic mushrooms and other natural psychedelic substances for individuals aged 21 and over.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
