<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>psilocybin on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/tags/psilocybin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in psilocybin on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/psilocybin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/oregon-psilocybin-2024/</guid>
      <description>Not Legal Advice Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice. The laws in Oregon, as with most places, are constantly changing, so do your own research and contact legal representation always.
Oregon Psilocybin 2024 Update: Navigating New Mushroom Laws and Program Insights Oregon&amp;rsquo;s landmark decision to legalize psilocybin for therapeutic use under Measure 109 has set a precedent for psychedelic therapy in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Amateur Mushroom Grow Part 1</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/amature-colorado-grow/</guid>
      <description>Not Legal Advice Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.
Intro In this series, we send a total newbie a grow bag and a liquid culture syringe to embark on the captivating journey to explore the art of mushroom cultivation, specifically focusing on the Golden Teacher variety of mushrooms, known for its enlightening properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin for Colorado Readers</title>
      <link>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/magic-quadrant/2024/colorado-psilocybin/</guid>
      <description>Not Legal Advice Disclaimer: This information is provided for general informational purposes only and should not be considered legal advice. We are not liable for any reliance placed on this content. Consult your local laws and seek legal representation for specific advice.
Overview In November 2022, Colorado voters passed Proposition 122 Legislative Council Draft, also known as the &amp;ldquo;Natural Medicine Health Act of 2022.&amp;rdquo; This groundbreaking legislation decriminalizes the possession, use, and personal cultivation of psychedelic mushrooms and other natural psychedelic substances for individuals aged 21 and over.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
