<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beginners on Rabbit Hole 223</title>
    <link>/categories/beginners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beginners on Rabbit Hole 223</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/beginners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Failed Grows, You Must Suck?</title>
      <link>/post/2025/failed-grows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2025/failed-grows/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Did I get your attention? Well, that was clickbait. The truth is, growing mushrooms &lt;strong&gt;isn’t always easy&lt;/strong&gt;. They are sensitive to temperature, moisture, contamination, and bacteria. While it can be challenging, the most important thing to know is that &lt;strong&gt;you can improve with practice&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Too many videos online make it look like you need to spend thousands of dollars and endless hours on your setup. Let me tell you—that’s not true.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beginner&#39;s Guide to Growing Mushrooms at Home Successfully</title>
      <link>/post/2024/beginners-guide-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2024/beginners-guide-part1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2024-03-01 Update with &lt;a href=&#34;https://midwestgrowkits.referralrock.com/l/RABBITHOLE22/&#34;&gt;Midwest Grow Kits&lt;/a&gt; Affilate links.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mushrooms have always fascinated me, and I&amp;rsquo;ve found joy in sharing this interest with others, especially those new to mushroom cultivation. Inspired by the informative and engaging content from creators like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@PhillyGoldenTeacher&#34;&gt;PhillyGoldenTeacher&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@therookiemycologist&#34;&gt;therookiemycologist&lt;/a&gt;, I embarked on my own mushroom growing journey. Despite the challenges faced during my initial attempts, each failure was a step closer to understanding the delicate balance required for successful mushroom cultivation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
